3lamodak.com 2013-10-04

# Privacy Policy

We are 3LAMODAK.com, is totally committed to protecting the privacy of our site visitors and customers. The 3LAMODAK team members are customers themselves of other Internet sites and fully appreciate and respect the importance of privacy on the Internet.

We will not disclose any of your personal information to third parties except where it’s a part of our service. You can visit and browse our website without having to provide any of your personal details.

If you have any comments or suggestions, we would be pleased to receive them at our 3lamodak postal address or you can send us email at info@3lamodak.com

**Note: -** Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without prior notice. Please periodically visit our website to make sure about any latest on privacy policy.

**SharingPersonal Data & Information** ****

**  
** We may collect your personal information when you register to 3lamodak.com. We collect, store and process your data for processing your purchase on our website. We need your personal information when you place an order for any product displaying on our website. We will store your personal information in a secure environment. We may store below information:

  *  Name, Gender, Postal Address, Delivery Address
  * Telephone Number, Mobile Number, Fax Number
  * Payment Details, Payment Card Details Or Bank Account Details
  * Transaction history
  * Communications record

We will not share any of your personal information like name, address, e-mail address, credit card information or other personal information with third parties without your permission, but we are not responsible or liable for the misuse of your personal information from third party sites if you have linked or been directed to the 3LAMODAK website.

**Communication & Marketing** ****

**  
** If you are registered with 3LAMODAK.com website than we will send you our daily deals, deal news and special offers via e-mail, post or telephone number.We may share your personal information with 3LAMODAK Merchants. As well as we provide special offers from our merchants (referred to as “3LAMODAK Merchants”) who, as part of the offer, request information on 3LAMODAK customers who purchased the offer in order to aid redemption. In that case, we will share your Personal Identity with 3LAMODAK Merchants. We have already informed to merchants that they are only permitted to communicate with customer for the purposes of the specific promotion or special offers with 3LAMODAK. We are not responsible for the actions which are taken by the 3LAMODAK Merchant because those are not in our control.

**Opt out** ****

3LAMODAK provide all users or customers with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving newsletters of marketing emails or promotional communications from us on behalf of our partners.

If you don’t want to continue to receive newsletters or marketing emails from us or selected third parties than, please contact us at [info@3lamodak.com](mailto:info@3lamodak.com) or you should click on the link located at the bottom of the email and follow the instructions in order to be removed from all future mailing. You can also opt-out by visiting 'My Data' in 'Your Account' on the 3lamodak.com website.

**Cookies** ****

We use "cookies" to collect information to assign each visitor a unique identification to understand the user's personal interests. A cookie can’t read your computer’s data or hard drive. Our advertisers or partners may also assign their own cookies to your browser because sometimes user clicks on their ads, we can’t control that.

Our website automatically collects limited information about your internet connection, IP address, when you visit our website. Your IP address does not identify you personally. We use this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to measure website traffic within our site and let our advertisers or business partners know the customers’ geographic locations from where they visited our website.

**Protecting your security** ****

We take appropriate security measures to protect personal information provided by you against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. Personal information that you provide may be disclosed for credit reference or fraud prevention agency, which is only for keeping a record of your information which include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

**Transfers of your Information** ****

Unfortunately, transmissions made via the Internet or telecom or other networks cannot be completely secure. We will try our best to protect your personal data or personal information, but we can’t give guarantee the security of data transmitted to our website and any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized acts of third parties.

**Disclosures of your information** ****

We may disclose your personal information to any of our business partners of affiliates. We may also disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * 3LAMODAK sells or buys any business or assets in the events
  * 3LAMODAK or all of its assets may be acquired by a third party, in this case personal data of customers may be one of the transferred assets

**Third party sites or Links to Other Sites** ****

Our website might be containing links to other websites and getting links from the websites of our affiliate partner networks, advertisers and other third parties. We may use third parties or partner websites to assist us with delivering best products to you, to help us to collect payments from you, analyzing data and also provide us with customer service support. We may share your personal information with third parties for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction. We may transfer our databases with your personal information if we sell our business or part of it. Please note that we are not responsible or liable for the privacy policies or content of those third parties or other sites. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

**Verifying your Details** ****

Do you want to verify your personal details which you have submitted to 3LAMODAK? You may contact us via e-mail or address given below. Our security procedures mean that we ask to you for proof of identity before we reveal your information. We will take your e-mail address and password detailswhen you have submitted upon registration. You will be responsible for any action which we take in response to a request from someone using your e-mail and password. We would strongly recommend that you don’t use the browser's password memory function as that would allow other people to access your personal information.

**Contacting us** ****

If you believe that any information which we are collecting on you is incorrect or incomplete, please send us an email as soon as possible, at the below mentioned address. We will definitely correct any information found to be incorrect.We are always ready to hear from our customers (even if it’s a complaint!). If you would like us to stop processing your information, please do not hesitate to contact our customer support team, who will be delighted to answer any of the questions you may have.

**You can contact us at**[ **support@3lamodak.com**](mailto:support@3lamodak.com) **or write to us at:-  
**  
**3LAMODAK**

**SAUDI ARABIA, JEDDAH AL HAMRA, ARAFAT STREET**

**PO BOX 140922 JEDDAH 21333 Tel: +966543874487**

**E-Mail:**[ **info@3lamodak.com**](mailto:info@3lamodak.com) **,** ****[**support@3lamodak.com**](mailto:support@3lamodak.com)

**Time: -Sat - Wed (10.00 am - 4.00 pm)**
